http://www.traderjoes.com/home/privacy-policy

Skip to main navigation.
Skip to main content.
Skip to side bar.
12/31/19
At Trader Joe’s, we understand that you care how information about you is used and shared. We care too
. As such, we make sure we safeguard your personally identifiable information and honor your requests for privacy.
The following note outlines our privacy practices and commitments:
What Kind of Information Are We Talking About?
Trader Joe’s gets information from and about you in a number of different ways through your use of our website, including:
Contact Information
Customer Inquiries:
When you choose to reach out to us through our customer inquiry forms, we store your questions along with personally identifiable information
(name, email, and phone number (should you opt to share it). We make note that we intend to use this information to communicate with you to offer customer service.
We also provide you the option to elect not to be contacted by third parties, such as our vendors.
The Fearless Flyer and e-Newsletter Communications
When you choose to sign up to receive the Trader Joe’s Fearless Flyer and/or our e-Newsletter, we store your personally identifiable information
(such as name, mailing address, phone number and/or email) in an electronic database. If at any time you do not want to receive our Fearless Flyer or e-Newsletter,
please update your preferences
on our website or select the “Unsusbscribe” option at the bottom of our e-Newsletter.
Job Applications:
When you choose to apply for a job through our website, we will collect information
(name, address, email, phone number, recent employment, and/or resume)
that you provide in the course of submitting that application. That information will be submitted to the provider of our online career portal, Avature, for
evaluation purposes. We encourage you to review  Avature’s Privacy Policy.
Site Navigation Information
When you use our website, we or our third-party service providers may collect information about how you access, use, or otherwise interact with our website
and e-Newsletter. This information is collected for various reasons, including ensuring that our website/e-Newsletter is functioning correctly, to understand how
our customers are using our website/e-Newsletter, to make improvements to our website/e-Newsletter experience, or to make our content more relevant to our
customers. The information collected may include technical information such as your IP address, the type of browser/device/hardware that you use to access the
website, the operating system on your device, the website or other online service that directed you to our website, and the content that you are viewing.
In other words, the information is only used for general analytical needs. That’s it.
We use Google Analytics to learn about how you and other customers use the website. You can learn more about how Google uses the information
it collects at:  https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
Cookies (not the edible kind)
Whenever you interact on our site, we receive and store certain information in the form of Internet “cookies.” You can’t eat them and neither can we.
Cookies are stored on your hard drive—not on our site—in the form of a text file (they are not harmful, nor tasty). They can help us understand your browsing
patterns, which allows us to provide targeted information about products and pricing. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically
deleted at the end of a session when you close your browser. Some cookies are called “persistent” cookies because they do not expire when you close your browser
. Don’t worry, though—you can remove them by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.
We do NOT use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after leaving the Trader Joe’s website. We have better things to do.
How does traderjoes.com use the information that it receives?
Trader Joe’s uses the information it receives to better serve you and other customers by:
Communicating about our products, stores, events and promotions
Notifying customers of product recalls
Responding to questions, requests or concerns and providing customer service
Administering contests and sweepstakes
Facilitating social sharing
Considering or responding to interest in working with us
Evaluating and improving our products and services
Analyzing customer use of our site
Trader Joe’s does not tie information to individuals for marketing purposes or sell your personal information to others.
It’s just not how we operate.
How does traderjoes.com use the information that it receives?
With Trader Joe’s Employees
Access to customer information is limited to employees who need it for a business purpose, such as to serve customers or maintain our information systems.
All employees are committed to following our Privacy Practices. That means employees will only use customer information to better serve you.
With Trader Joe’s Partners
We may also provide a list of names and addresses to a mail house so that they can send our newsletter from us to you. We may also share information with
companies we have contracted with to provide technology services. Any partner that we work with would be required to sign a nondisclosure agreement that would
prohibit them from disclosing the information we provide them to anyone else.
With Other Parties
Other than in the above situations, we may release your information ONLY if you request or authorize us to do so. We may also release customer information
when we believe it is necessary to comply with the law, enforce our legal rights; or to protect our customers or us.
We will NEVER sell your personal
information to anyone, for any reason, at any time. Never.
What About Links to Third-Party Websites?
Our site sometimes provides links to websites that are operated solely by third parties that are not under our control. These Privacy Practices apply to
our site only, and is not intended to describe the privacy policies of any third-party sites.
Okay, Trader Joe’s - How Safe is My Information, Really?
We Are Serious About The Security of Your Information:
We make reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is protected while you are on our site. We have security procedures in the storage and
disclosure of personal information, which are designed to prevent unauthorized access.
It’s
exactly the kind of protection that what we would want, if we were surfing the web on another site.
It’s really that simple.
Changes in Our Privacy Practices and Commitments
We are always improving and updating our website to further enhance your experience. As a result, our policies will continue to evolve.
As we implement new technology and provide new services, we will update our Privacy Practices & Commitments accordingly. Any changes to our Privacy
Practices & Commitments will take effect upon posting. We encourage you to refer to this page on an ongoing basis for our most current policy and practices.
Your Part
By using our website, you are consenting to the collection, use and sharing of the information described in this statement of Privacy Practices &
Commitments. We appreciate your trust in us and we promise to protect it fervently.
If you would like to review or make requests related to your personally identifiable information as it exists in our records, please contact Trader Joe’s at:
Trader Joe’s
PO Box 5049
Monrovia, CA 91017-7149
(Attention: Privacy Officer)
privacy@traderjoes.com
We use cookies on our website to improve the customer experience.
By continuing to enjoy our site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies (the kind that are full of bytes vs the kind you bite).
For more information on how we collect and use this information, please review our Privacy Policy Got It
